Miten Dave

I want to work and enhance my skills Machine Operator.

Brampton, ON mitendave3_99u@indeedemail.com 647-673-3132

I am very disciplined and have time management skills. I like to keep the machines well maintained for smooth operations. I want to gain more experience working with machines.

Work Experience

MATERIAL HANDLER

NATIONAL LOGISTICS SERVICES July 2020 to September 2020

I had to be quick and accurate in performing my tasks, which included loading - unloading of merchandise, packing the merchandise after it was entered in the company's system, and placing it at the right location using pump-truck, so that the merchandise of different clients can be located easily.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE, GORE CONVENIENCE

Gore Convenience - Brampton, ON July 2019 to February 2020

I had to deal with variety of customers with varying demands. It was a fast-paced environment and I had to meet each customer's need, that too being quick and accurate, to serve the upcoming customers.

CNC Machine Operator

Magna International Inc - Mississauga, ON August 2019 to January 2020

It was fast-paced environment where I had to meet daily targets. Every day I was supposed to set up the machine and make operating adjustments. I was

responsible to check the quality of parts as per the requirements. I had to report daily production targets to my team leader including the downtime and scrap quantity.

Education

DCS / DEC in ELECTROMECHANICAL ENGINEERING TECHNICIAN

SHERIDAN COLLEGE - Brampton, ON January 2019 to December 2020

BACHELOR OF MECHANICAL ENGINEERING in MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

V.V.P ENGG. COLLEGE June 2014 to May 2018

Skills

- CNC Machine Operator (Less than 1 year)
- Mazak
- Pallet Jack
- Picker Packer
- Warehouse Associate
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Microsoft Excel
- General Labour

Links

http://www.linkedin.com/in/miten-dave

Certifications and Licenses

Co-Curricular Record

May 2020 to Present